<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>rftg on GrooveStomp</title>
    <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/tags/rftg/</link>
    <description>Recent content in rftg on GrooveStomp</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://127.0.0.1:1234/tags/rftg/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Swapping RftG in for Dice Masters</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/05/07/swapping-rftg-in-for-dice-masters/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/05/07/swapping-rftg-in-for-dice-masters/</guid>
      <description>During a slight bit of downtime today I separated my Dice Masters decks back into the cards that came with the starter set and those that didn&amp;rsquo;t. My Dice Masters gaming buddy came over, and instead of Dice Masters, we played two games of Race for the Galaxy!
My buddy has soundly beat me the last three games of Dice Masters that we&amp;rsquo;ve played. That&amp;rsquo;s great since we now know he has graduated well past the student phase, but it&amp;rsquo;s also illustrated some parts of Dice Masters that neither of us are super keen about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RftG: The Gathering Storm</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/05/01/rftg-the-gathering-storm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/05/01/rftg-the-gathering-storm/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s always been my intention to pick up The Gathering Storm if I picked up Race for the Galaxy because of its solo support. Well, today I completed that transaction and also managed to finish my first playthrough of the real, physical copy of RftG. I played against the easy robot, and I won! 43-32, in fact. That may actually be my largest win to date.
It was interesting. Playing against Keldon&amp;rsquo;s AI sure streamlines playing the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RFTG - First Win!</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/17/rftg-first-win/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2015 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/17/rftg-first-win/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp;
Not a lot to see here. I pursued a strategy involving a combination of production and exploration. Hopefully the first in a complex and long-lasting relationship. :-)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RFTG on Linux</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/17/rftg-on-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2015 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/17/rftg-on-linux/</guid>
      <description>Through the magic of Wine (specifically the PlayOnLinux variant) I&amp;rsquo;m now able to play RFTG on my Ubuntu machine from System 76. Oh happy day! :-)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Race for the Galaxy</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/17/race-for-the-galaxy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/17/race-for-the-galaxy/</guid>
      <description>I know what the next game I am going to buy &amp;ldquo;for me&amp;rdquo; is going to be. Apparently Roll for the Galaxy is a more friendly iteration of the game. At least Tom Vasel and Sam Healey think so. I can&amp;rsquo;t speak to that, though. I&amp;rsquo;ve been playing the Keldon AI to learn the game, and I must say: I am hooked. I started last night and couldn&amp;rsquo;t stop thinking about it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>