<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>programming on GrooveStomp</title>
    <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/tags/programming/</link>
    <description>Recent content in programming on GrooveStomp</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://127.0.0.1:1234/tags/programming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Coding Practice</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2016/01/19/daily-coding/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2016/01/19/daily-coding/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve mentioned before that I&amp;rsquo;ve begun what I call &amp;ldquo;daily coding practice.&amp;rdquo;1 My inspiration for this comes directly from Mike Acton by way of HandmadeCon2. Mike said that we as serious, professional programmers should be dedicating some slice of time every day to practicing our craft, even if it&amp;rsquo;s as little as 30 minutes. Now, Mike also emphasized small, throw-away practice, similar to doing scales if you were to practice guitar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ludum Dare (2015-12-12)</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/12/12/ludum-dare/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/12/12/ludum-dare/</guid>
      <description>Ludum Dare 34 kicks off this weekend. There are two themes that tied: &amp;ldquo;two button controllers&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;growing.&amp;rdquo; I was fully intending to participate, but I am having serious doubts about that decision now. I&amp;rsquo;ve managed to build the tiniest of skeletons of an application, but I have so much to do in order to get anywhere near a working game that I know it&amp;rsquo;s basically infeasible. This is pretty much the reality when you have kids and a full time job and you&amp;rsquo;re already doing daily programming practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data and Domain Isolation</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/09/19/data-and-domain-isolation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/09/19/data-and-domain-isolation/</guid>
      <description>Today I present some scattered thoughts on organizing data and logic in programs.
I&amp;rsquo;m starting with MVC because it&amp;rsquo;s pervasive and well understood. As a pattern for wrangling complexity, it&amp;rsquo;s solid because it&amp;rsquo;s so simple: organize your program into three main components and that&amp;rsquo;s how you deal with complexity. As a bonus, the file organization of your program can just follow the pattern and use three folders. This simplicity makes it easy for new teammates to understand what&amp;rsquo;s going on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balancing Development Considerations</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/09/16/balancing-development-considerations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/09/16/balancing-development-considerations/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s common knowledge that changes are cheap to accomodate early in the lifecycle of development. The extent to which this is true can feel rather visceral, depending on the competing needs of the project and the available resources.
Programming is an iterative process involving a lot of in-the-trenches work, some reflection, and a lot of effort to address technical debt. I think it&amp;rsquo;s really important to partake in this holistic view of software development regardless of the day-to-day realities of the office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interested in Efficiency</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2014/11/23/interested-in-efficiency/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2014/11/23/interested-in-efficiency/</guid>
      <description>Casey Muratori started Handmade Hero. It&amp;rsquo;s his project to teach C programming to beginners by building a game from scratch using the most minimal subset of operating system calls possible. I&amp;rsquo;ve been attending as many of the live streams as I can, and the whole project fills me with excitement. Earlier this year Mike Acton gave a talk at CppCon titled Data Oriented Design and C++. I watched this video and watched it again, and again and again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ruby Loadpath Confusion</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2014/04/29/ruby-loadpaths/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2014/04/29/ruby-loadpaths/</guid>
      <description>The main application at work was developed in Ruby on Rails, with supporting services written in Java and PHP. We&amp;rsquo;ve recently rewritten the PHP service in Java, but haven&amp;rsquo;t fully deprecated the old PHP code yet. All of our applications and services run on Amazon&amp;rsquo;s AWS.
Going forward we will be trying to gut our monolithic app into many services, and we&amp;rsquo;re using Vert.x as the underlying technology core to do that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chef Dependency Management</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2014/02/25/chef-dependencies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2014/02/25/chef-dependencies/</guid>
      <description>At work we&amp;rsquo;ve been using Chef to manage systems automation. It&amp;rsquo;s been a bit of a rough process with only one devops team member. Around five months ago I started pitching in. This served two purposes: test our existing process and help out with more pressing automation tasks. It became quite obvious that our use of Chef required a lot more discipline and structure. We&amp;rsquo;re not fully there yet, but we&amp;rsquo;re definitely making improvements.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>