<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GrooveStomp</title>
    <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/</link>
    <description>Recent content on GrooveStomp</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://127.0.0.1:1234/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>VPS Learning</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2019/02/27/vps-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2019/02/27/vps-learning/</guid>
      <description>Today we learn how little I know about system administration.
I host most of my own &amp;ldquo;cloud&amp;rdquo; services on a VPS I rent from SSDNodes. Recently I purchased an upgraded KVM node for reasons of which I&amp;rsquo;ll get into later. Anyway, I ran into a hiccup while trying to start migrating from my older VPS.
└─ curl 142.44.184.204 curl: (56) Recv failure: Connection reset by peer  Hmm.
NOTE: First of all, I know the machine is reachable because I can SSH into it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RISC-V, Go and QEMU</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2019/02/13/riscv-go-qemu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2019/02/13/riscv-go-qemu/</guid>
      <description>I finally took the opportunity to jump back into RISC-V, Go and QEMU as a followup to my previous exploration.1
I had a difficult time understanding exactly what was required to run my compiled Go program in QEMU. Let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at the instructions.2
 Compile and run in qemu-riscv64 (which is expected to be in PATH):
$ GOARCH=riscv GOOS=linux go run ../riscvtest/add.go  Build:
$ GOARCH=riscv GOOS=linux go build .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PostgreSQL Password Encryption</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2018/12/12/chkpass/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2018/12/12/chkpass/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m working on a side project to gain more exposure to different kinds of projects in Go. This one is a pretty typical web application involving multiple authenticated users. For data storage I&amp;rsquo;m using PostgreSQL for its UUID type and cryptographic extensions. The cryptographic extensions are interesting, because of things like chkpass1.
My project right now is using chkpass for storing user passwords. Almost immediately after hooking this up I started wondering how chkpass actually works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>qemu and RISC-V</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2018/12/07/qemu-riscv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2018/12/07/qemu-riscv/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a long time since I&amp;rsquo;ve posted here. So what&amp;rsquo;s up?
I&amp;rsquo;ve been working at Lendesk in a team lead / senior developer role and trying to pursue my interest in Go and Linux. This has been a very tricky path to navigate as work has abandoned any pretense of plans to adopt Go and all work machines are MacOS. Thankfully, I&amp;rsquo;ve been able to carve out some personal time to keep poking around in my area of interest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android: Mainframe</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2017/05/17/android-mainframe/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2017/05/17/android-mainframe/</guid>
      <description>After lunch today I made a visit to a local boardgame store just to see what was new. The local gamestore near my place is much cheaper, but has a drastically different selection, so it&amp;rsquo;s always nice to see what else is available.
There were two notable games on today&amp;rsquo;s visit:
 Agricola: Family Edition Android: Mainframe  I&amp;rsquo;ve seen mention of Agricola: Family Edition before, so that was neat to see in person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Race for the Galaxy Android</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2017/05/09/rftg-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2017/05/09/rftg-android/</guid>
      <description>Race for the Galaxy is out now on Android1.
This features Keldon Jones&amp;rsquo; AI2 and is the best digital version I&amp;rsquo;ve seen. It translates wonderfully and is easily worth the ten bucks.
Footnotes 1Race for the Galaxy on Google Play
2Keldon Jones&amp;rsquo; Race for the Galaxy AI</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Editor Sizes</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/post/2016-11-24-editor-sizes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/post/2016-11-24-editor-sizes/</guid>
      <description>A few months ago I was starting to get irked at the relatively poor performance of Emacs on my primary development system. Emacs isn&amp;rsquo;t terrible, but it is noticeably slow compared to Vim. So, for the sake of curiosity I decided to look at some executable sizes. I started by just doing a simple:
ls -alh `which &amp;lt;editor&amp;gt;`  But that only captures the size of the executable on disk without regard for any shared libraries or dynamic memory allocations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Applications</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/post/2016-11-10-android-applications/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/post/2016-11-10-android-applications/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been getting frustrated with my computing experiences lately. I won&amp;rsquo;t go into many details here, but my frustration has extended to my smartphone and has spurred me to investigate alternatives to many programs and services I&amp;rsquo;ve been using.
Provided for your benefit here is a list of several Android programs I&amp;rsquo;ve recently discovered. I&amp;rsquo;m not vouching for these yet, and may not even have much experience with them yet, but they are here and may serve you well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HandmadeCon 2016 and Self Hosting</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/post/2016-10-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/post/2016-10-30/</guid>
      <description>HandmadeCon 2016 is just around the corner! I&amp;rsquo;m really excited to go! The speaker lineup looks absolutely stellar this year.  Besides that, I&amp;rsquo;ve obviously been keeping myself busy for a few months here with nary an update. The most visible change to anyone who might read this blog is that I&amp;rsquo;ve completely revamped my hosting situation; both making great progress on my goal of being entirely self-hosted, and for serving up content via HTTPS to you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linuxing</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2016/05/26/linuxing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2016/05/26/linuxing/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever heard of suckless1? I think I stumbled onto suckless sometime while reading K. Mandla2, though there&amp;rsquo;s a reasonable chance it might have happened before then. suckless immediately resonated with me because of their philosophy3. Their software also looks good, very accurately reflecting the idea of minimalism4; often requiring you to rethink how you typically interact with software to do what you want to do. Sometimes this process of re-evaluation is fruitful, sometimes maybe less so, but it&amp;rsquo;s always interesting to experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bluetooth on Arch</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2016/05/13/bluetooth-arch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2016/05/13/bluetooth-arch/</guid>
      <description>Well, today I had a &amp;ldquo;fun&amp;rdquo; little diversion. I started out by wanting to connect a game controller to my crappy little Dell Mini so I can start prototyping some games. Of course a controller isn&amp;rsquo;t required, but I like controllers and it seemed like a small little learning exercise. If you know me and my experience with computers, then you&amp;rsquo;ll know that this didn&amp;rsquo;t go as planned. Also, why would I be writing about it if it did?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brief Update for 2016-05-11</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2016/05/11/brief-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2016/05/11/brief-update/</guid>
      <description>I haven&amp;rsquo;t been too active here or on my daily coding project1. So what&amp;rsquo;s been going on? Honestly, not too much. A lot of Dark Souls. I mean watching VaatiVidya2  and EpicNameBro3 while also playing through Dark Souls: Prepare to Die Edition4 and Dark Souls II: Scholar of the First Sin5. I love that series so much. I&amp;rsquo;m not very good at it and I don&amp;rsquo;t like everything that the games do or that the community is interested in; but overwhelmingly I am completely entranced by it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I like KDE</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2016/04/11/kde/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2016/04/11/kde/</guid>
      <description>So, it turns out I like KDE.
I use Ubuntu a lot. It&amp;rsquo;s installed on all of my computers and it&amp;rsquo;s the server OS I&amp;rsquo;ve used at work for the past five or so years. Typically I stick with Unity on the desktop. There are a few reasons why I opted to change: I like to try new things, I get bored, I haven&amp;rsquo;t used KDE in a while. It&amp;rsquo;s hard to say exactly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Reviews, OSes and the 3DS</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2016/02/03/game-reviews-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2016/02/03/game-reviews-update/</guid>
      <description>Today is a grab-bag of miscellaneous thoughts and updates that aren&amp;rsquo;t necessarily related to each other.
First off, I haven&amp;rsquo;t been keeping up with my daily programming practice, but it&amp;rsquo;s not for lack of will. As my last post may have illustrated 1; I&amp;rsquo;ve been dealing with computer problems. I&amp;rsquo;ve only recently managed to get a working installation of Windows on my machine, but I&amp;rsquo;ve run into problems with my GNU/Linux distro, so actual productivity work is put on hold until that&amp;rsquo;s resolved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UEFI and Windows 10</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2016/02/02/bad-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2016/02/02/bad-software/</guid>
      <description>My primary desktop environment is some variant of GNU/Linux. The only case where this hasn&amp;rsquo;t been true is when I was really into PC gaming and was operating off of Windows 7 for that purpose.
Recently I&amp;rsquo;ve been more interested in privacy. One nice thing you can do several modern GNU/Linux distributions is full disk encryption (FDE). I&amp;rsquo;ve been using this where possible for over two years now. Unfortunately, FDE requires the GNU/Linux distro to completely take over your HDD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Update On Self-Hosting Progress</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2016/02/28/self-hosting-struggles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2016/02/28/self-hosting-struggles/</guid>
      <description>Well, it seems I&amp;rsquo;m making very slow progress towards my goal of self-hosting. The first issue I&amp;rsquo;ve run into is with officially support OSes. I like running Arch Linux, but Arch Linux is not officially supported by either OwnCloud or GitLab. GitLab is the more demanding of the two applications, requiring a minimum of 2GB of RAM and strongly recommending 2 cores. Unfortunately, I have Manjaro (an Arch distribution) running on my Dell Mini 10 where I installed GitLab via Yaourt; but that machine only has 1GB of RAM and a single core.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self Hosting</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2016/02/25/self-hosting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2016/02/25/self-hosting/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m going to start this post with a little problem I created for myself.
So many computers Let&amp;rsquo;s see here. I have a gaming desktop at home, a work laptop at work, a netbook at home for resource-constrained programming and a Raspberry Pi. That&amp;rsquo;s cool. Daniela also has her own computer, but that&amp;rsquo;s hers and I simply leave it be. Two weeks ago I caught myself watching The 8-Bit Guy talking about the Macbook Core Duo and seeing if it&amp;rsquo;s obsolete1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MatthewMatosis</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2016/01/23/matthewmatosis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2016/01/23/matthewmatosis/</guid>
      <description>This is a short post. I really like videogames, but I often find myself lacking motivation to play. I think this happens a lot because I know there&amp;rsquo;s a serious time commitment to actually complete most games and I&amp;rsquo;m not normally able to play for more than an hour or so.
Well, Dark Souls has been absolutely consuming my free time lately.
I got quite into Dark Souls about a year ago when I picked up a copy for PC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Coding Practice</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2016/01/19/daily-coding/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2016/01/19/daily-coding/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve mentioned before that I&amp;rsquo;ve begun what I call &amp;ldquo;daily coding practice.&amp;rdquo;1 My inspiration for this comes directly from Mike Acton by way of HandmadeCon2. Mike said that we as serious, professional programmers should be dedicating some slice of time every day to practicing our craft, even if it&amp;rsquo;s as little as 30 minutes. Now, Mike also emphasized small, throw-away practice, similar to doing scales if you were to practice guitar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ludum Dare (2015-12-12)</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/12/12/ludum-dare/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/12/12/ludum-dare/</guid>
      <description>Ludum Dare 34 kicks off this weekend. There are two themes that tied: &amp;ldquo;two button controllers&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;growing.&amp;rdquo; I was fully intending to participate, but I am having serious doubts about that decision now. I&amp;rsquo;ve managed to build the tiniest of skeletons of an application, but I have so much to do in order to get anywhere near a working game that I know it&amp;rsquo;s basically infeasible. This is pretty much the reality when you have kids and a full time job and you&amp;rsquo;re already doing daily programming practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bernband Review</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/11/10/bernband-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/11/10/bernband-review/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m drawn to the idea of walking simulators. It&amp;rsquo;s no coincidence that my first &amp;ldquo;intentional&amp;rdquo; game review was of Proteus. Modern so-called &amp;ldquo;AAA&amp;rdquo; gaming is full of violence, so walking simulators are a nice conceptual departure. I don&amp;rsquo;t have a lot of experience with walking simulators, but I have played a few, including: Dear Esther, Proteus, Shelter, The Stanley Parable and Gone Home. Even among that small selection, there&amp;rsquo;s a wide variation of gameplay and themes, so clearly this is a broad genre worth exploring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proteus Review</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/10/20/proteus-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/10/20/proteus-review/</guid>
      <description>The best way I can think of to open this review is by quoting myself: “What a weird, boring, delightful, pleasant game. It is really difficult to feel [it] or describe it in one way.”
Proteus is boring. You walk around and have very little agency in the world. You can chase creatures and not much else. I really wish days could be shortened to 5 minutes instead of the current shortest value of 15 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inspired to Share Gaming Experiences</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/10/19/pc-gaming/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/10/19/pc-gaming/</guid>
      <description>This past weekend was a little bit rough. Dee and I were both feeling really under the weather so we pretty much got as little done as possible. Dee took over responsibilities for dropping Lily off with her folks, so I jumped at the opportunity to catch up on a few shows. Among them was Jodorowski&amp;rsquo;s Dune, a film I found to be rather inspirational.
For a long time now I&amp;rsquo;ve felt rather disillusioned with modern AAA videogames.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data and Domain Isolation</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/09/19/data-and-domain-isolation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/09/19/data-and-domain-isolation/</guid>
      <description>Today I present some scattered thoughts on organizing data and logic in programs.
I&amp;rsquo;m starting with MVC because it&amp;rsquo;s pervasive and well understood. As a pattern for wrangling complexity, it&amp;rsquo;s solid because it&amp;rsquo;s so simple: organize your program into three main components and that&amp;rsquo;s how you deal with complexity. As a bonus, the file organization of your program can just follow the pattern and use three folders. This simplicity makes it easy for new teammates to understand what&amp;rsquo;s going on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balancing Development Considerations</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/09/16/balancing-development-considerations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/09/16/balancing-development-considerations/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s common knowledge that changes are cheap to accomodate early in the lifecycle of development. The extent to which this is true can feel rather visceral, depending on the competing needs of the project and the available resources.
Programming is an iterative process involving a lot of in-the-trenches work, some reflection, and a lot of effort to address technical debt. I think it&amp;rsquo;s really important to partake in this holistic view of software development regardless of the day-to-day realities of the office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Friday</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/08/29/thoughts-on-friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/08/29/thoughts-on-friday/</guid>
      <description>I just finished playing another two rounds of Friday. Just four more to go until I&amp;rsquo;ve hit ten plays and can focus on the other titles in my 10x10 challenge. Even when I hit that point, though, I&amp;rsquo;ll be looking forward to playing Friday between other games.
I tried two different strategies today, neither of which really panned out.
Strategy 1: Remove Low-Scoring Cards The goal here is to remove any negative or zero pointed cards to strive for a maximally productive deck.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going For Ten</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/08/27/boardgaming-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/08/27/boardgaming-update/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t recall if I&amp;rsquo;ve ever explicitly mentioned on here the 10x10 challenge for boardgaming. I don&amp;rsquo;t know it in-depth, but what I recall is essentially to play 10 boardgames you already own 10 times within the calendar year. The theoretical advantage of doing this is less time spent buying new games, and more time spent playing games you already own. What a fantastic idea! Especially for someone like me, who likes to read and research and buy when getting into a new hobby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A return... to LOTR:LCG</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/05/20/a-return-to-lotr-lcg/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/05/20/a-return-to-lotr-lcg/</guid>
      <description>With my last post being on the 13th, it seems as though I&amp;rsquo;ve had a slight hiatus from gaming. For the most part, I would agree with this. I managed to play some D&amp;amp;D and Ascension via my phone.
Tonight, however, I made a triumphant return to form with my first session of LOTR:LCG since I built my foamcore insert. I used this guide for deckbuilding with just one core set and played Passage Through Mirkwood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More on The Witcher</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/05/14/more-on-the-witcher/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/05/14/more-on-the-witcher/</guid>
      <description>Well, I got two more games of The Witcher Adventure Game under my belt this evening. The first game I played was supposed to go to 3 quests, but I quit after two. Man, that was incredibly frustrating. One thing that became very apparent is how little interaction there is among players. This is more of a &amp;ldquo;multiplayer solitaire&amp;rdquo; game than any other game I&amp;rsquo;ve played. I seriously just open a browser window and do something completely differently while the computer opponents play their roles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Witcher Adventure Game</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/05/12/the-witcher-adventure-card-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/05/12/the-witcher-adventure-card-game/</guid>
      <description>GOG is having an &amp;ldquo;up to 85%&amp;rdquo; off sale for their Witcher series of games. I already have The Witcher 1 and 2, but they&amp;rsquo;re also offering The Witcher Adventure Game. I was part of the beta, but didn&amp;rsquo;t have an opportunity to play it, and only attempted to play the demo a couple of times. I found the tutorial wasn&amp;rsquo;t particularly elucidating and just let it be. I&amp;rsquo;ve been curious about the boardgame for some time, but don&amp;rsquo;t know anybody who&amp;rsquo;s played it, and haven&amp;rsquo;t seen it come up very often in any boardgame discussions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marvel Legendary - Secondary Play</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/05/10/marvel-legendary-second-play/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/05/10/marvel-legendary-second-play/</guid>
      <description>I decided to give it another go. I played the following setup:  Scheme: Secret Invasion of the Skrull Shapeshifters Mastermind: Magneto Henchmen: Savage Land Mutates Heroes: Captain America, Hulk, Deadpool  I think that&amp;rsquo;s all that&amp;rsquo;s important. The Scheme says to use 6 heroes and put 12 hero cards into the villain deck. This conflicts with Solo rules which state to use 3 heroes, so I just halved the number of hero cards to add to the villain deck to 6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marvel Legendary via Vassal</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/05/09/marvel-legendary-via-vassal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/05/09/marvel-legendary-via-vassal/</guid>
      <description>As any reader of this blog is probably aware, I started playing Dice Masters a short while ago. Coincidentally, the second Avengers movie was released within the last two weeks and I had the opportunity to watch that with a friend. I am absolutely certain that this confluence of events has left me thinking about Marvel Legendary.
The Legendary games from Upper Deck are well regarded. I first started getting into them either as a result of watching tons of reviews of boardgames, or as a result of being super interested in deckbuilding games and then watching a bunch of reviews of boardgames.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swapping RftG in for Dice Masters</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/05/07/swapping-rftg-in-for-dice-masters/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/05/07/swapping-rftg-in-for-dice-masters/</guid>
      <description>During a slight bit of downtime today I separated my Dice Masters decks back into the cards that came with the starter set and those that didn&amp;rsquo;t. My Dice Masters gaming buddy came over, and instead of Dice Masters, we played two games of Race for the Galaxy!
My buddy has soundly beat me the last three games of Dice Masters that we&amp;rsquo;ve played. That&amp;rsquo;s great since we now know he has graduated well past the student phase, but it&amp;rsquo;s also illustrated some parts of Dice Masters that neither of us are super keen about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Friday - From Monday</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/05/05/more-friday-from-monday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/05/05/more-friday-from-monday/</guid>
      <description>Wow.
So I just tallied my score and got -1. I may have miscounted. We can say -7 if we want to err on the safe side. Either way I&amp;rsquo;m super happy about it. My last score was -23 or so. There&amp;rsquo;s been a steady progression with every game I&amp;rsquo;ve played. This time I was able to make it to the third phase whereas my previous best was only part way through the second phase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunday Gaming</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/05/04/sunday-gaming/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/05/04/sunday-gaming/</guid>
      <description>I just wrapped up two rounds of Onirim. I aborted the first one because it was obvious I couldn&amp;rsquo;t win, and I realized I hadn&amp;rsquo;t been following all of the rules. I decided to just start playing through the expansions one-by-one and see how it works. Tonight was the first expansion: The Book of Steps Lost and Found. There&amp;rsquo;s a mechanic where you can cast &amp;ldquo;spells&amp;rdquo; that aid you, and I simply wasn&amp;rsquo;t doing that at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RftG: The Gathering Storm</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/05/01/rftg-the-gathering-storm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/05/01/rftg-the-gathering-storm/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s always been my intention to pick up The Gathering Storm if I picked up Race for the Galaxy because of its solo support. Well, today I completed that transaction and also managed to finish my first playthrough of the real, physical copy of RftG. I played against the easy robot, and I won! 43-32, in fact. That may actually be my largest win to date.
It was interesting. Playing against Keldon&amp;rsquo;s AI sure streamlines playing the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LOTR:LCG Foamcore Insert</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/29/lotr-lcg-foamcore-insert/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/29/lotr-lcg-foamcore-insert/</guid>
      <description>I built my first foamcore insert! See my imgur album here.
I made a reddit post here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What did you play this week (Apr 20 - Apr 26)?</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/27/what-did-you-play-this-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2015 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/27/what-did-you-play-this-week/</guid>
      <description>The reddit thread.
My contribution.
Reproduced here:  Friday: Such a great solo game. I&amp;rsquo;m steadily improving, but also not playing it as much as I&amp;rsquo;d like. Partially because of all the other great games out there, but also because it&amp;rsquo;s surprisingly intense.
Pandemic: The Cure: Such a great game. I recently rated this as my only 10&amp;frasl;10 game on the appropriate /r/boardgames thread. Played it with my neighbor at the local gamestore yesterday and he loved it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friday Update</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/27/friday-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2015 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/27/friday-update/</guid>
      <description>I just finished my third real playthrough of this highly rated single player game. My score this time? -23. That&amp;rsquo;s a solid progression!  Playthrough 1: -50 Playthrough 2: -42 Playthrough 3: -23  I definitely felt like I was making better decisions this time, too. I also noticed a few spots where I can focus my attention next time.
Man, such a great solo game. A bit intense, though; I find it difficult to play it multiple times in succession.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foiled!</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/27/foiled/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2015 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/27/foiled/</guid>
      <description>I sprung for my own personal copies of Race for the Galaxy and Patchwork today. I sneakily jammed them into my boardgaming shelf in broad daylight, with the wrapping still on. Being the suave husband that I am, I also didn&amp;rsquo;t mention a word to Dee. Well, after dinner she found her way into the den and noticed the shiny new wrap on several games on the wall. The jig is up!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some Words on Iconography</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/26/some-words-on-iconography/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/26/some-words-on-iconography/</guid>
      <description>Race for the Galaxy gets a lot of flack for its iconography. I think most of this flack is undeserved. The iconography on the cards is there to prevent players having to frequently refer to the rulebook. Most of the icons are very intuitive, and the ones that aren&amp;rsquo;t are accompanied by a descriptive block of text which typically immediately elucidates the meaning of said icons.
Dee and I had guests over last night for boardgaming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LOTR:LCG: A Deck in Review</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/25/lotr-lcg-a-deck-in-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2015 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/25/lotr-lcg-a-deck-in-review/</guid>
      <description>I recently built a custom deck to take me through the first scenario. It worked wonderfully that first shot, and that felt great; though I was a little surprised it worked as well as it did. Tonight I gave it a second test drive and definitely ran into some kinks.
My selection algorithm for pulling cards from various spheres of influence was to simply go for all the low-cost ones. Everything 0 or 1 point got scooped up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EOD - 2015-04-24</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/25/eod/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2015 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/25/eod/</guid>
      <description>Just finished off the night with two rounds of LOTR:LCG followed by base Onirim.
LOTR:LCG, man. There are definitely a lot of complex interactions in those cards and lots of things to think about when playing. I know I am underutilizing Beravor&amp;rsquo;s 2-card draw ability. I guess that comes with exposure, though.
Onirim is nice. I&amp;rsquo;ve won the base game the last two times I&amp;rsquo;ve played it now, so I know it&amp;rsquo;s time to move on to the expansions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VivaJava: The Coffee Game: The Dice Game</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/24/vivajava-the-coffee-game-the-dice-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2015 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/24/vivajava-the-coffee-game-the-dice-game/</guid>
      <description>One of the greatest names in boardgaming history. Go on, just say it out loud to yourself a few times.
I ordered this game based mostly off of a reddit comment which suggested this was one of the best dice games out there. The reason I even read that comment was because I was riding high off of Pandemic: The Cure and was looking for another dice game to tempt Dee with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Latest Temptations</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/24/latest-temptations/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2015 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/24/latest-temptations/</guid>
      <description>Being the sophisticated gamer that I am, I&amp;rsquo;m constantly on the lookout for new games to pick up. There are all kinds of games for all types of situations. A very brief overview of what has been on my mind in the past couple months goes like this:  Games with proper solitaire modes Games that play well with two Gateway games Deckbuilders  In the last week or so I&amp;rsquo;ve really started thinking about games that support 4+ players for those times when we invite guests over specifically for boardgaming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LOTR:LCG: Round Two</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/21/lotr-lcg-round-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2015 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/21/lotr-lcg-round-two/</guid>
      <description>Wow. Okay, so that was a completely different experience.
I&amp;rsquo;ve played a total of five times now, I believe. I have a reasonable understanding of the mechanics of the game, and of what various cards do. I haven&amp;rsquo;t been getting much luck with the prebuilt decks I&amp;rsquo;ve tried (either custom or part of the core set), so I figured I might as well just try my own thing. Even more than that, I threw caution to the wind and went for something that I think I read as being uncouth: a 3-faction deck.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lord of the Rings: The Card Game</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/21/lord-of-the-rings-the-card-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2015 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/21/lord-of-the-rings-the-card-game/</guid>
      <description>Lord of the Rings: The Card Game, a.k.a Lord of the Rings: LCG, a.k.a LOTR:LCG - which is how I&amp;rsquo;ll refer to it from now on.
This game&amp;hellip; I don&amp;rsquo;t know about it. I was really excited to get my copy after having read a lot about how it&amp;rsquo;s a great game to play solo. One thing you&amp;rsquo;re not told is how the core set isn&amp;rsquo;t very good for solo play, and how only one of the three included missions is even beatable if you play solo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What did you play this week (Apr 13 - Apr 19)?</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/20/what-did-you-play-this-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/20/what-did-you-play-this-week/</guid>
      <description>From the Reddit thread.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a copy of my post there:  D&amp;amp;D Dice Masters, Bang! The Dice Game, Race for the Galaxy (Keldon&amp;rsquo;s AI), Shadowrun Crosssfire, Escape
Dice Masters: Battle for Faerun: My wife does not like this game at all, but all my gamer friends love it. I&amp;rsquo;ve learned that the way I play would benefit most from multiple copies of the starter set instead of getting any boosters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RFTG - First Win!</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/17/rftg-first-win/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2015 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/17/rftg-first-win/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp;
Not a lot to see here. I pursued a strategy involving a combination of production and exploration. Hopefully the first in a complex and long-lasting relationship. :-)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RFTG on Linux</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/17/rftg-on-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2015 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/17/rftg-on-linux/</guid>
      <description>Through the magic of Wine (specifically the PlayOnLinux variant) I&amp;rsquo;m now able to play RFTG on my Ubuntu machine from System 76. Oh happy day! :-)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Race for the Galaxy</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/17/race-for-the-galaxy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/17/race-for-the-galaxy/</guid>
      <description>I know what the next game I am going to buy &amp;ldquo;for me&amp;rdquo; is going to be. Apparently Roll for the Galaxy is a more friendly iteration of the game. At least Tom Vasel and Sam Healey think so. I can&amp;rsquo;t speak to that, though. I&amp;rsquo;ve been playing the Keldon AI to learn the game, and I must say: I am hooked. I started last night and couldn&amp;rsquo;t stop thinking about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bang! The Dice Game</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/17/bang-the-dice-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2015 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/17/bang-the-dice-game/</guid>
      <description>I picked up Bang! The Dice Game at Strategies two weeks ago while browsing for Fiasco and Savage Worlds. I&amp;rsquo;ve really been looking forward to playing it since, but the opportunity simply wasn&amp;rsquo;t available until today. I booked a conference room and four of us got together over lunch to play three bouts. It&amp;rsquo;s a nice game; simple to comprehend, plays quickly and offers opportunities for subterfuge. It seems like it would really start to shine with 5 players, and may be best with the upper limit it supports of 8 players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RPG Backstories</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/15/rpg-backstories/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2015 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/15/rpg-backstories/</guid>
      <description>My favourite part of D&amp;amp;D to date has been pouring over resources and thinking up a backstory for my character.
I don&amp;rsquo;t have a long history with tabletop RPGs other than being interested in D&amp;amp;D for many, many years. In 2014 I was lucky enough to have coworkers who were interested in playing, as well as a wonderful GM. We started a D&amp;amp;D 4th edition party. That was a good experience, but something about it didn&amp;rsquo;t really feel right to me; it wasn&amp;rsquo;t particularly engaging and the game felt repetitive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friday</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/15/friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2015 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/15/friday/</guid>
      <description>I just finished my first legitimate game of Friday. -50 points.
At one point I understood the game would be difficult, but I must have just glossed over that detail. There may be a little masochist living inside me who jumps for joy at the thought of things like Dark Souls and 1001 Spikes. Certainly I can appreciate those things, but I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if I outright enjoy them&amp;hellip;
When I first read through the rules, I immediately attempted a playthrough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Shadowrun: Crossfire diversion</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/15/a-shadowrun-crossfire-diversion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2015 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/15/a-shadowrun-crossfire-diversion/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve really been struggling with Shadowrun: Crossfire. I love the theme to death and the mechanics work nicely. There&amp;rsquo;s just something off about it. For one thing, it&amp;rsquo;s punishingly hard; I&amp;rsquo;ve played 8 times and lost every single one. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem to matter whether I&amp;rsquo;m playing single player, two player or three. (Haven&amp;rsquo;t tried four yet.) The best progress I&amp;rsquo;ve made was playing four runners solo.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been toying with the idea of reworking the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interested in Efficiency</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2014/11/23/interested-in-efficiency/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2014/11/23/interested-in-efficiency/</guid>
      <description>Casey Muratori started Handmade Hero. It&amp;rsquo;s his project to teach C programming to beginners by building a game from scratch using the most minimal subset of operating system calls possible. I&amp;rsquo;ve been attending as many of the live streams as I can, and the whole project fills me with excitement. Earlier this year Mike Acton gave a talk at CppCon titled Data Oriented Design and C++. I watched this video and watched it again, and again and again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Position at Mogo</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2014/10/14/started-at-mogo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2014/10/14/started-at-mogo/</guid>
      <description>I am super excited to announce that I have started working at Mogo Financial. Mogo is doing really interesting things in the Canadian financial market and I am proud to be a part of it.
My title is officially Senior Software Developer, though I have a lot of learning and growing to do.
I look forward to working with my new team and the challenges we will be facing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ruminations on Writing</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2014/09/21/ruminations-on-writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2014/09/21/ruminations-on-writing/</guid>
      <description>As my blog has become neglected, I&amp;rsquo;ve had ample time to contemplate my approach to writing. When I reflect on my habits it is clear that I haven&amp;rsquo;t been directing my attention and energy where they could most effectively be applied.
Not all of my thinking has been negative or quasi-constructive, though; some of it has been generative. As an example, I&amp;rsquo;ve really been wanting to write about computer graphics. The scope of what I want has changed wildly from a few simple one-off C++ programs to a strongly-typed Haskell-style rendering and animation engine written in C++.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ruby Loadpath Confusion</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2014/04/29/ruby-loadpaths/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2014/04/29/ruby-loadpaths/</guid>
      <description>The main application at work was developed in Ruby on Rails, with supporting services written in Java and PHP. We&amp;rsquo;ve recently rewritten the PHP service in Java, but haven&amp;rsquo;t fully deprecated the old PHP code yet. All of our applications and services run on Amazon&amp;rsquo;s AWS.
Going forward we will be trying to gut our monolithic app into many services, and we&amp;rsquo;re using Vert.x as the underlying technology core to do that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proposing a Talk for !!Con</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2014/03/09/bangbangcon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2014/03/09/bangbangcon/</guid>
      <description>I am writing a proposal for a 10 minute &amp;ldquo;lightning talk&amp;rdquo; at !!Con. I feel like this is a relatively normal thing that shouldn&amp;rsquo;t warrant any special writing. But there are a couple of things that make it a very standout thing for me.
 It is in New York. Dee is super excited about the possibility of visiting New York. I&amp;rsquo;ve never been before. What an excellent excuse to go visit!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chef Dependency Management</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2014/02/25/chef-dependencies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2014/02/25/chef-dependencies/</guid>
      <description>At work we&amp;rsquo;ve been using Chef to manage systems automation. It&amp;rsquo;s been a bit of a rough process with only one devops team member. Around five months ago I started pitching in. This served two purposes: test our existing process and help out with more pressing automation tasks. It became quite obvious that our use of Chef required a lot more discipline and structure. We&amp;rsquo;re not fully there yet, but we&amp;rsquo;re definitely making improvements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resetting</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2014/02/24/resetting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2014/02/24/resetting/</guid>
      <description>It seems like every blogger is susceptible to a refresh or reset at least once in their amateur life. Well, it&amp;rsquo;s time for me to succumb once more.
Daniela and I are more proud than I ever could have imagined to welcome Lily into our lives. To celebrate we&amp;rsquo;ve decided to buy ourselves our first home! All this positivity is the perfect catalyst to start a brighter, more positive online persona for myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/about/</guid>
      <description>I write cloud applications and developer tools. I entered the industry due to my enthusiasm for computer games and 3d graphics. These days I&amp;rsquo;m writing server side applications in high level scripting languages and the tools to assist in maintaining them.
I have been a programming language enthusiast, having played with: (* indicates I have been compensated for it.)
 ActionScript* Bash C C++* Clojure* Common Lisp Emacs Lisp Factor Go* Haskell* Java* Javascript* Lua PHP* Perl* Prolog Python Ruby* Rust Scala* SQL* Scheme Vimscript  I would summarize my thoughts as:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All Posts</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/all_posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/all_posts/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Programming</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/programming/</guid>
      <description>What follows is a really rough, high-level outline of topics I want to address. I may never actually get around to doing this, but I&amp;rsquo;m keeping it here for now as a reminder.
Various programming concepts. The plan is to write tutorials covering each of the topics listed here.
Computer Graphics  Creating a GUI
 Software Rendering
 3D Math
 Vectors Transformations Matrices Quaternions  Cameras
 Rigid Follow Camera Delayed Folow Camera Cameras as Objects  User Interfaces</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/projects/</guid>
      <description>Daily Programming Practice After the first HandmadeCon I was motivated to try a little dabble of programming every day. I have long since stopped doing that, but I still use that repo to explore new projects on occasion.
 Software Renderer I decided to do a &amp;ldquo;clean-room&amp;rdquo; implementation of a software renderer to replicate what it might have been like as a graphics/game programmer in the early/mid 1990s.
 C Parser HandmadeHero and The Jeff and Casey Show motivated me to start exploring making my own language and development tools.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
