<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>friday on GrooveStomp</title>
    <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/tags/friday/</link>
    <description>Recent content in friday on GrooveStomp</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://127.0.0.1:1234/tags/friday/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Friday</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/08/29/thoughts-on-friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/08/29/thoughts-on-friday/</guid>
      <description>I just finished playing another two rounds of Friday. Just four more to go until I&amp;rsquo;ve hit ten plays and can focus on the other titles in my 10x10 challenge. Even when I hit that point, though, I&amp;rsquo;ll be looking forward to playing Friday between other games.
I tried two different strategies today, neither of which really panned out.
Strategy 1: Remove Low-Scoring Cards The goal here is to remove any negative or zero pointed cards to strive for a maximally productive deck.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Friday - From Monday</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/05/05/more-friday-from-monday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/05/05/more-friday-from-monday/</guid>
      <description>Wow.
So I just tallied my score and got -1. I may have miscounted. We can say -7 if we want to err on the safe side. Either way I&amp;rsquo;m super happy about it. My last score was -23 or so. There&amp;rsquo;s been a steady progression with every game I&amp;rsquo;ve played. This time I was able to make it to the third phase whereas my previous best was only part way through the second phase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friday Update</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/27/friday-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2015 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/27/friday-update/</guid>
      <description>I just finished my third real playthrough of this highly rated single player game. My score this time? -23. That&amp;rsquo;s a solid progression!  Playthrough 1: -50 Playthrough 2: -42 Playthrough 3: -23  I definitely felt like I was making better decisions this time, too. I also noticed a few spots where I can focus my attention next time.
Man, such a great solo game. A bit intense, though; I find it difficult to play it multiple times in succession.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friday</title>
      <link>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/15/friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2015 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://127.0.0.1:1234/2015/04/15/friday/</guid>
      <description>I just finished my first legitimate game of Friday. -50 points.
At one point I understood the game would be difficult, but I must have just glossed over that detail. There may be a little masochist living inside me who jumps for joy at the thought of things like Dark Souls and 1001 Spikes. Certainly I can appreciate those things, but I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if I outright enjoy them&amp;hellip;
When I first read through the rules, I immediately attempted a playthrough.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>